WETHER FORECAST!
When did you steal it?
Was it just now when you got
blown away by Jolyne's punch?
You must return it.
Give it back to me this instant!
You cannot comprehend the forces
with which we're meddling in.
Do you finally remember
everything now, Pucci?
Look up there. It's coming.
Those rainbows...
Look at them all!
It's heavy forecast!
The Devil's Rainbow!
Weather?
What's your deal?
What are you doing?
what was that for yo
answer me i was sitting in
that seat you know get
your disgusting hands off
me you asshole i'll kill
you excuse
me sir that
bench is reserved for
patients at this hospital
i don't give a damn who it's for if
you really want him to sit so badly
Then how about you take the bench's
place and let him sit his ass on you?
Weather, what are you doing?
This guy isn't our enemy.
He's just a random doctor.
Why don't you plop down on
that, you fractured bastard?
I'm feeling a lot better now.
Hey, hang on.
Where the hell are you going, Weather?
Weather?
Who do you think you are?
So Weather Forecast is my new name.
Ah, well, I don't really
have a problem with it.
What's up with him all of a sudden?
It's almost as if...
He's a completely different person!
Never again!
It's been repeated by the
fate of the fate of the world?.
It's the sky to the sea!.
Getting through!.
The meaning of living in the world?.
Heavens fall me down.
It's the rainbows!
Here they come!
The rainbows are getting closer!
Jolene!
We don't have time to hesitate.
Things aren't looking good.
I'll finish you with one last blow!
My arm! What the hell?
Oh, Hermes!
Uh, yeah, what just happened?
Am I seeing things?
It's only gonna get worse.
Sure, you guys are in trouble,
but you're not the only ones.
Bastard, when did you...
You should take this as a warning.
Whatever happens, don't
touch the rainbows.
Father Poochie tried to stop all this.
These are weather forecasts, rainbows.
Weather Stan has the ability
to control the weather.
Do you understand what that means?
Now that his memories
have been returned to him,
he could even destroy the
ozone layer if he wanted to.
Do you get it?
The ozone layer is way
up there in the sky.
Do you know what'll happen if
weather decides to mess with it?
All I know is we'd be totally screwed.
Everybody will die.
Everybody!
It was a huge gamble!
But I'm going to use weather
forecast to my advantage.
so that I can continue to live.
What the hell did you do?
Was my arm melted because of
the destroyed ozone layer?
Answer us!
Are you saying that these rainbows mean
weather forecast has his memory back?
It's his subconscious.
Weather forecast stands sometimes
functions unconsciously.
The climate can be quite a
difficult thing to control,
so there are instances where it manifests
on its own without him even noticing.
The fact of the matter is, he never should
have had his memories returned to him.
Now listen.
In order to stop the rainbows,
you either need to kill
Weather or find a way
to extract his memories
from him once more.
Although, I don't believe you're capable
of taking Weather's life, Jolene.
And if you cannot, everyone here
will die before the new moon.
Well, that is everyone
except for me, of course.
I wouldn't let Versus
get away if I were you.
Versus is getting away too, Jolene!
Two women are down here.
Officer!
Where are we?
The hole was this shallow?
He must have deactivated Netherworld
when he ran off like a bitch.
Hey, which way?
Did you see two men run from here?
Where'd they go?
Before that, hold on.
I've seen you two somewhere.
Your faces were on some mug shots.
More rainbows!
What's going on?
They're outside, too!
Hey!
What the?
Don't move!
You ladies are the escaped prisoners!
Pull that right there!
Hey, get back here!
Kids, don't touch those rainbows!
Don't even go anywhere near them, okay?
Uh, hey, Jolene!
This is terrible.
How terrible. Whoa!
Unbelievable!
What is this phenomenon?
When you touch those rainbows,
snails come out of your body!
Weather Forecast was
able to make frogs rain
down from the sky during
a freak storm once.
But this situation is nothing like that.
What does this have to do with weather's
ability to control the weather?
And how does it connect to
this bizarre phenomenon?
On top of that,
there's something really strange about
the people who have snails on them.
It's like they're zombies!
This shit is fucked!
Hermes, careful!
Jolene!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
But you know, Hermes!
It could be that stand users Have a
higher tolerance to this phenomenon?
than everyday people.
So, Jolene, which one of them
are we going after first?
Who will be the first to get
their ass handed to them?
Is Weather Forecast our new enemy?
Or rather, are we going to continue
tracking down Father Poochie?
Who exactly are we supposed
to be fighting here?
This new Weather Forecast
to SS Memory's back.
He's our enemy, isn't he? No way!
Weather Forecast is an ally!
He's not an enemy!
But Versus still is!
Didn't you hear the priest?
He said not to let Versus get away.
Digging up the past is
his stand's ability.
He might be able to
excavate Weather's memory
disk and put an end to
this rainbow apocalypse.
All right, I see.
But if we want to catch up to him,
we've got to find our way
out of this hospital first.
Hey!
Where are you going, Weather?
Are you headed toward the
direction of Jolene or something?
Huh?
I want it too!
No, I need it!
Much more than that damn priest!
Before he can get to it, I have to get
my hands on the power to go to heaven,
and maybe then I can finally be
happy like I've always wanted.
Now there is only one thing
that I, Versus, need to do.
Dig there, Netherworld!
I found it!
I've excavated the memory held in the
ground of them arriving to the hospital.
Hey, Hermes.
Seeing as how we're closer to
tracking down Father Pucci,
this would be the safest time.
We should do it now.
Huh?
Giving the Speedwagon Foundation
the disc with my father's memory.
It's our best bet to give it to them
while I have the priest's attention.
I have faith that Emporio
can handle it himself.
Finally, my dad will be back to normal.
So the friend who Jolyne
Cujoh was talking to
over the radio earlier
goes by the name Emporio.
I have to find him then.
Not even Father Poochie knew a
thing about this mystery person.
I haven't dug up this Emporio guy's face
yet, so I don't know what he looks like.
But thanks to all of this mess,
it's likely that he hasn't had a
chance to meet with the Foundation.
and that means he's still in
possession of Jotaro Kujo's disc.
And from what the priest has told me,
he'll learn how to get to
heaven by reading said disc.
If I can get a hold of that disc,
I'll be able to go to heaven too!
And my only shot at it is while
these rainbows are still here!
Mark my words, I'm gonna
make Jotaro Kujo's disc mine!
What the hell?
These things keep multiplying and spreading
out all over the ground in layers!
It's a giant snail orgy!
The freaks are procreating
one after another!
Here's a fun fact snails
don't have a gender.
Whenever they pierce each other
with those tentacle things on
their heads they start popping out
babies all over the damn place.
Oh good fucking grief!
So it's an organism that can have
sex with anything it encounters?
huh.
To be honest I'm a little jealous.
Nuh-uh, that's actually disgusting!
Hermes! Yeah? Smack!
Stone Ocean!
Possessing two abilities
at once is impossible.
Weather Forecast's ability should
only be to control the weather.
But still, what is this?
What the hell is going on right now?
In ancient times,
what we know as oxygen
was created when the first
forms of plant life sprang
to existence on our Earth.
When an additional oxygen atom
attaches to the O2 oxygen molecule,
the gas becomes O3, which is more
commonly referred to as the ozone.
Unlike oxygen, ozone is quite dense.
It exists as a thick shell roughly 20 to
25 kilometers from the Earth's surface.
If one day the ozone layer were to
be suddenly destroyed completely,
what would happen to all living
things that reside on planet Earth?
Humans are not capable of
predicting weather anomalies.
As a result,
they can only work with
known data and hypothesize
about the weather using
past records and instances.
Just keep looking who
the hell could they be
her friend has to be
somewhere nearby I'll find
the Guy and when I do
I'll take it from him I
can't let him give joshiro
sisk to the foundation
I have to look out for the ones who
are headed to the hospital knowing
that jolene is still inside He
wouldn't run away like a coward the one
who heads toward the hospital to
help her must be Emporio I have to
keep my eye out for someone who's
reacting differently from everyone else
Dammit!
I'm not gonna lose this time!
No!
I'm gonna be happy at
the end of all this shit!
Okay, Jolyne, I want
to help you. But first,
I have to get your dad's
disc into the hands
of the Speedwagon Foundation's messenger!
I made a promise to her that I would
keep Jojiro's disc safe no matter what,
and that should be my top priority.
When I called the Foundation, they said
someone will be here in five minutes!
Shit! Shit!
Seriously, what the hell?
There isn't a single person
making their way to the hospital.
I thought finding him was gonna be easy.
Whoever he is, he has to
be somewhere around here.
Hey, Jolyne, is that you?
Hey, I did it!
All thanks to Netherworld!
I should have just asked
the ground from the start.
With Jolene's memories, it was simple
enough to find Emporio's phone number.
That must be the phone he used
to tell Jolene which seats
on the plane were safe so
she didn't die in the crash.
I just had to dig up the number from Jolene's
memory, and now I know the number too!
Still though I wasn't
expecting him to be a kid
a kid that not even the
priest knows about quite
a surprise huh huh wait
what the disc isn't even
on his body and where
did the phone go I could
have sworn it was just
in his hand am I losing
my mind hold on chill
out I can find where he
hid it by excavating his
memories and learn what
happened oh shit fuck me
they're coming this way
did versus really go
this way Jolene yeah I
can sense his presence
if I remember correctly
this is the way Emporio went too that's
weird huh do you think he could be after No,
there's no way.
Emporio's a secret.
Neither Versus nor the priest know of him.
Their body is... Emporio!
Not good. Dodge it!
This is gross.
These slimy bastards are
actually real snails.
They're so slippery.
And I don't think this
freaky shit is an illusion.
Huh?
Ugh!
Hermes, no!
Jolene, don't you worry about me.
Just go after Emporio.
I saw him getting dragged
away, too, in that bush.
I don't know what Versus is up to,
but he's definitely after Emporio!
Stone Ocean!
Damn it.
Even the rope!
My body has become as slow as a snail!
Emporio!
If you can hear me,
grab a hold of my rope!
And pull it!
Forty-five-sixty!
Hot, hot, hot! Huh?
Jolene!
Don't forget we're in Florida.
They love football here.
Why don't you go play some?
Hey, Jolene Cujo, enjoy getting
dragged into the end zone.
No, the rope!
You can't do anything moving that slowly.
Bye, it'll take you a while
to get back over here.
Oh yeah, it's dangerous if
I touch these things too.
There's no mistake a
moment ago he was still
holding on to the memory
disc of Jolene's father.
But a split second later
the disc vanished out
of thin air is this
Emporio stand ability he's?
Storing and extracting items
from somewhere that must be
how he hid it but how do i find
Where he's keeping the disc
i'll take another look what
Jolene's gone but where to she
shouldn't be able to move that
fast in her current conditions!
I can't friggin' believe it.
She got him!
She rolled over to get close!
With her body all soft
and slimy right now,
she easily slid inside of the
broken pipe to make her move!
Now she's gonna fuck you up!
Another world!
I'll admit you surprised
me with that rolling stunt!
But with the state you're currently in,
compared to my netherworld,
you're basically powerless.
Meanwhile, I dug up more memories,
like the memory of the salt
from the evaporated seawater.
After all, if you want to
get rid of slugs or snails,
salt is their ultimate weakness.
What?
Anyway, where is it?
I know Emporio was hiding the
disc somewhere on his person.
Does he have a secret pocket?
He's gotta be hiding
it inside of something!
Huh?
Oh, I see.
Our stands are rather similar.
So his stand's ability is
storing the memories of objects.
I actually did it!
Jotaro Kujo's disc belongs to me!
It's finally in my hands!
I won!
Now with this,
I'm one more step closer to attaining what
Father Poochie has been searching for!
Chuline!
I'm really sorry, Emporio.
If this was going to
work, I had to use you.
But I'll be able to save
everyone because you touched me.
And luckily, he touched you as well.
Now he's feeling the
sensation all at once.
What's happening?
I can't move forward at all.
Nice!
You managed to pin him down this time!
Way to go, Jolene!
Emporio.
It's no use.
The Speedwagon Foundation's
courier's stuck,
So they're on standby until
they can get closer to the city.
I see.
Oh, nice! Hotwire!
You still got it, former car thief?
Oh, come on!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm innocent regarding that
whole stolen car incident!
I know, I'm just playing.
You're gonna be coming with us.
I wouldn't try running away if I were you.
I couldn't even if I tried.
Huh?
Where's the driver?
They were here before,
and now the seat's empty.
But all that's left are these shells.
Hmm.
Even more shells.
Hold on. I think...
I think I'm starting to understand it.
Wow Weather.
I don't know what you did to
cause these snails to show up,
or how it's even possible.
But now I'm starting to get an idea
of how this phenomenon's going to end.
It's their predators!
These bugs hunt down the snails
in order to feed on them!
Naturally, snails move slow as hell, so
being devoured is how they usually go out.
So in situations like this one,
the bugs crawl into their shells, bite
into their heads, and suck on their flesh!
And it's because of
this gruesome method of
eating that these bugs are
known as snail suckers!
Yo, Weather!
I said to wait! Hey!
What's going on?
Is the one who caused this madness you?
Weather!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Shut your mouth, Anastasia.
That man, he's heading
closer to us as we speak.
At this point, he's somewhere
within a 20 meter radius.
By he?
Do you mean the priest?
He's here.
My only reason for
continuing to live is to
settle the score with
him once and for all.
Of some place.
Other than he.
Although you think I smile.
Inside and all the while.
I'm wondering.
About my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.